<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>DDA Security and More (Continued)</name>
  	<packageId>Mlie.DDASecurityAndMore</packageId>
	<author>Mlie</author>
	<url>https://github.com/emipa606/DDASecurityAndMore</url>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.0</li>
		<li>1.1</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies />
	<loadAfter />
	<description>Update of James76543s mod for RimWorld 1.1
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1356331773
with the turrets from the original mod from DaemonDeathAngel
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=892434137

[img]https://raw.githubusercontent.com/emipa606/RimWorld-Wrapper/master/Notice.png[/img]

Support-chat:
https://discord.gg/SuhwVpM

Non-steam version:
https://github.com/emipa606/DDASecurityAndMore
	
--- James76543s Description ---
I love the walls from this mod, so I updated it to V1.0 version. I left out the turrets (couldn't figure out how to update them, and I feel that More Vanilla Turrets handles this a lot more nicely anyway).

7/28/2019 I changed the recipe (to require some chemfuel) and changed balance around a little so reinforced walls are slightly less expensive that four regular walls back to back, but at the cost of greater work.

For V1.0, I made some changes to be aware of. I removed the coolers and heaters, I modified some minor settings for the walls, and I remove the custom workshop table completed. You can now make reinforced plates from the smelter, no need for an extra workshop table! I also added embrasures that are stronger than normal and have a custom texture.

--- Original Description ---
Hey, Onesan, lets mine through this idiots puny wall and lay waste to everyone and everything within!


                                         Added Content                          

Re-Inforced Walls                    |  Requires Steel Plates
Blast Door                           |  Requires Steel Plates
Re-Inforced Manned Shotgun Turret    |  Requires Steel Plates
Re-Inforced Manned Sniper Turret     |  Requires Steel Plates
Re-Inforced Manned Gattling Turret   |  Requires Steel Plates
Barbed Wire                          |  Does Not Require Plates
Fences                               |  Does Not Require Plates

                                         Known Issues

Currently No Known Mod Conflicts

Update Error:
With the recent update, I broke some peoples saves by changing def names, if you are recieving errors about missing def names, just place down a new metal working table and remove the old one, that should fix your errors on save and reload. If you had wood re-inforced walls, you will have to create a new game in order to use the mod, as wooden reinforced walls were removed, and will cause saves to fail.

Report a conflict in the "Bug Report" Thread.

                                         Change Log

4-02-2017 : 16:45 Changelog
Wood Walls No Longer Capable of Being Reinforced
Cooler Material Cost Fixed
Turrets Added
Reinforced Wall Flamability Removed
Fixed Conflict With http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=756216922.

By massive request, the description has been changed to somewhat further explain what the mod does!

Thanks you to BaRKy from youtube for the awesome Mod Showcase!
Go and show this guy some love.
https://www.youtube.com/user/BaRKy1911

Wall and Fence textures by mrofa and Abrexus</description>	
</ModMetaData>
